immigratemanitoba.com 2011-12-31

# Province of Manitoba | Privacy Notification

This policy applies to the handling of personal information that is collected via the Manitoba government website.

**Logging of Site Visitors**  
Like most web servers, the Manitoba government server collects some information about visitors to the site. However, the server only logs the domain name of visitors. Depending on the setup of your internet service provider (ISP), this information may identify who you are; you may wish to contact your ISP for more information in this regard. The log data is analyzed for trends, security and statistics, and then aggregated.

If you have any questions about the information gathered automatically by our website, please contact the webmaster at [webmaster@gov.mb.ca](mailto:webmaster@gov.mb.ca).

**Collecting Personal Information to Provide Requested Services**  
Any personal information that you provide through the Manitoba government's website is collected in compliance with The Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy Act (FIPPA). The personal information that you provide will be used only for the purpose(s) for which it is collected, unless you consent or we are authorized to do so by FIPPA.

If you wish to have a brochure or other publication mailed to you, we will request your name and address.

In some other instances, it may be necessary for us to collect additional personal information in order to provide you with the service that you want. When personal information other than your name and mailing address is collected, you will be notified of

  * the purpose for which the information is being collected 
  * the legal authority for the collection 
  * the title and business address (including email address) of an official who will answer any questions you may have about the collection of the information 

If you have questions concerning the collection of personal information on a Manitoba government web page, please contact the official listed on that page.

If you have any general questions about Manitoba’s Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy Act, please visit the [FIPPA website](http://www.gov.mb.ca/fippa).
